Shrikant Kunte

Pune. 411007 • +91-7875902395

• shrikantkunte30@gmail.com • https://www.linkedin.com/in/shrikant-kunte-960348125/

Senior Software Engineer | Full Stack Development | React/JavaScript/NodeJS Developer

A FULL STACK developer with 6+ years of experience in developing end-to-end products. I have experience in the design, development and implementation of Web Applications, data analytics and APIs using ReactJS, NodeJS, SQL, JavaScript, Python and Java-API. I have Worked on Agile methodology using Jira in product development.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- **Programming Languages.** JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, Python.
- Web Technologies. ReactJS, Redux, NodeJS, HTML, CSS/MaterialUI/Bootstrap
- Database. MySQL, PostgreSQL
- Mobile App. React Native, Ionic Frameork3.
- Standard Analytical Tools. Athena, OHDSI atlas, webapi, Achilles, CohortDiagnostics.
- Hand On Experience. Data Structure, Database, System Design.
- **Software or Services or App Servers or Dev Tools.** Postman, Tomcat, GIT, Jenkins, docker, Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ, Maven, Gradle

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Engineer (Great Software Laboratory, Pune) Aug 2021 - Present

- Designed and developed dynamic UI components driven by JSON config stored in DB.
- Involved in the development of APIs using reactive Java.
- Developed UI of in-house developer portal (Similar to APIGEE).
- Technology Used ReactJS, Redux, JavaScript, TypeScript, Java, Git, Jenkins.

Software Engineer (Sarvaha Systems Private Limited, Pune) Aug 2017 – July 2021

- Developed an application to manage the workflow of utility location management.
- Worked on developing a web app to display Veterans Cemetery using GIS data stored on GeoServer.
- Developed a Python-based ETL pipeline to transform General Practitioners and Hospital datasets into OMOP CDM.
- Implemented algorithms like PheKB and OHDSI phenotypes in SQL and Python to extract CRC and T2DM patients' data from the dataset.
- Created a mobile app to display proprietary GIS data stored on GeoServer with additional features like user location tracking and user authentication.
- Technology Used React JS, JavaScript, NodeJS, MS SQL Server, PostgreSQL, Python, React Native, Ionic Framework, MapBox, OpenStreetMap, OHDSI analysis tools, tomcat, Docker.

EDUCATION

SGGSIE&T, Nanded Jun 2013 - May 2017 BTech in Computer Science